dllkit.com 2018-11-19

# Privacy And Information Security Policy

### Introduction

DLLKITSTER LTD is committed to safeguard the privacy of its customers and individuals who make use of our online facilities. This policy provides you with information about what data we collect and how this data is processed by us. We try to make our Privacy Policy easy to understand so that you are informed as to how we use your information. This Policy explains what personal information we collect from you, why we collect it and how we use it. 

If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us, at [support@dllkit.com](mailto:support@dllkit.com). 

### What Personal Information Do We Collect?

Identifying Information Submitted by You  
You are not required to register to view our Site. However, registration is required to purchase our Software, when registering we may ask you to submit your name and email to us. If you wish to purchase our Software you must provide your credit card information to our third party payment processor. We do not collect or store your payment information, such information is subject to our third party payment processor’s Terms of Service and Privacy Policy. 

Non-Identifying Information  
Whenever you visit our Site, we may collect non-identifying information from you, such as your IP address, interactions with the Site and Service, referring URL, browser, operating system, cookie information, usage, data transferred and Internet Service Provider. Without a subpoena, voluntary compliance on the part of your Internet Service Provider, or additional records from a third party such as your wireless provider, this information alone cannot usually be used to identify you. 

We work with the following payment processing partners.  
Paddle.com Market Limited - <https://paddle.com/privacy>   
NEXWAY, S.A.S. - <https://corporate.nexway.com/legal-notice-privacy/>   
Their Terms and Privacy Policies are always linked to from the shopping cart, and so is the name of the processing partner who will handle your payment. 

We work with the following analytics and promotion services:  
Google Analytics - <https://termsfeed.com/blog/privacy-policy-google-analytics/>   
Google Adwords - <https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/54817?hl=en>   
Yandex Metrics - <https://metrica.yandex.com/about/info/privacy-policy>

We may use Remarketing for our software and services promotion. To opt out from the remarketing, please visit this url: <http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/>   
Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as Flash to collect and store information.   
To manage Flash LSOs please follow this url <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>

### What we may do with the Information we collect?

We use information you provide to fulfill your request and improve our products and services. We may use personal information to display or send personalized content to our website visitors as well as to send newsletter, product features, promotional material, special offers and other updates to our customers and newsletter subscribers. A subscriber may, at any time, opt out of receiving such information. We also use collected information to evaluate and administer our products and services, resolve customers' issues like respond to any problems that may arise such as product delivery failures, difficulties in navigating our sites or accessing certain features as well as to gauge user trends to determine what products are most popular with users. 

We allow users of our website to email us their queries. We do not retain any email address (unless you are a member who already has voluntarily provided your email address) of either the sender or recipient of such e-mail or links after they are sent. 

### Changing and erasing information

If you would like to make changes to the information DLLKITSTER LTD has on you, such as update your email address, or if you want to have all information DLLKITSTER LTD has on you permanently deleted from company records, you may send a message to support@dllkit.com any time. You may also request to have a copy of all information we have on you by emailing us at the same address. 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

### Sharing Your Personal Information

We do not share, sell, rent or trade your personal information with third parties other than as disclosed within this privacy policy. We may share certain personal information with trusted vendors to carry out a transaction you have requested (e.g., sharing card payment information with our credit card processor to obtain payment of fees and to activate your subscription to the Service). We use Live Chat to assist you if you have questions while using our site or regarding your order. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for promotional purposes. 

We may collect and possibly share your personal information to enforce the Terms of Service. This may be done to prevent a crime or violation of our Terms or to help solve a transgression that has been committed. 

### Cookies

To make this site work properly, we sometimes place small data files called cookies on your device. Most big websites do this too. 

### What are cookies

A cookie is a small text file that a website saves on your computer or mobile device when you visit the site. It enables the website to remember your actions and preferences (such as contact information and other display preferences) over a period of time, so you don’t have to keep re-entering them whenever you come back to the site or browse from one page to another. 

### How cookies are used

Cookies collect information about the use of our website. This information includes:  
Type of Internet browser  
Operating system  
Domain name of the site from which you connect  
Date and time  
Duration of your visit  
Number of visits  
Average time spent on our website  
Average time spent on the pages that you view  
A cookie also contains a unique identification number that identifies your browser. This helps us recognize your browser when you visit our website again. 

For marketing and statistical purposes, we use both first-party and third-party cookies: 

Enabling these cookies is not strictly necessary for the website to work, but it will provide you with a better browsing experience. You can delete or block these cookies, but if you do that some features of this site may not work as intended. These cookies do not cause any harm. 

By continuing to browse this site you are agreeing to our use of cookies. 

### How to control cookies

You can control and/or delete cookies as you wish – for details, see aboutcookies.org. You can delete all cookies that are already on your computer and you can set most browsers to prevent them from being placed. If you do this, however, you may have to manually adjust some preferences every time you visit a site and some services and functionalities may not work. 

### Changes to Privacy Policy

We will occasionally update "Privacy Policy" as necessary to protect you to comply with a changing environment. We recommend that you check the policy when you visit our site to be sure you are aware of and understand the prevailing policy. If we make material changes to this policy we will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. We will not make material changes in how we may handle any of your previously collected personal information that have retroactive effect unless legally required to do so, and we will e-mail registered customers and newsletter subscribers information on material changes to this policy. 

### Law Enforcement

You agree that we may disclose your information to authorities if compelled to by a court order. Additionally, you agree that we may disclose your information if we reasonably believe that you have violated a law or the terms of our Terms of Service, Software License Agreement or Privacy Policy or if we believe that a third party is at risk of bodily harm. In the event that we receive a subpoena affecting your privacy, we may elect to notify you to give you an opportunity to file a motion to quash the subpoena, or we may attempt to quash it ourselves, but we are not obligated to do either. You release us from any damages that may arise from or relate to the release of your information to a request from law enforcement agencies or private litigants. We may release your information under the conditions listed in this paragraph whether it is to individuals or entities and to any state or Federal authorities within the United States, or elsewhere. 

### Children's Privacy

Our Service is not intended to be used by children. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. 

### Changes to Privacy Policy

We will occasionally update "Privacy Policy" as necessary to protect you to comply with a changing environment. We recommend that you check the policy when you visit our site to be sure you are aware of and understand the prevailing policy. If we make material changes to this policy we will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. We will not make material changes in how we may handle any of your previously collected personal information that have retroactive effect unless legally required to do so, and we will e-mail registered customers and newsletter subscribers information on material changes to this policy. 

### Contact information

For further queries, please e-mail us at [support@dllkit.com](mailto:support@dllkit.com) or you can drop a mail at: 

DLLKITSTER LTD  
Suite 2, 4 Queen Street, Edinburgh, United Kingdom, EH2 1JE
